不会有任何结果
could ever come of this
因为我仍然爱着我的妻子
because I'm still attached to my wife,
这是实话
and... I'm just being honest.
这是你表达我们要均摊的方式吗
Is this your way of saying we're gonna split the bill?
香槟
Erm, champagne.
当然均摊  威士忌  谢谢
Definitely splitting the bill. Whiskey, please.
-什么类的  -大的
- Any particular sort? - Large.
真有见识
Oh, discerning.
知道吗  吃一大口止痛药就能一了百了
You know what? It's a mouthful of painkiller.
真有意思  阴暗  沉重
This is good schtick. You know, dark and down.
但你显然不是真的想自杀  吓人而已
But you're obviously not really suicidal. It's just bullshit.
嗯  这你可就说错了
Right, that's where you're wrong.
我知道你的故事  不过说真的
No, I know the story. But seriously though,
自杀有多难
how hard is suicide?